What's this?
Mila?
My words hold no magic...
It's been a while.
I see you took the throne with no issues.
Valt?
Who in the world are you?
~ Joyful Sorrow ~
I didn't expect you to absorb
Simila's physical components.
You're the one who manifested Simila?!
I am.
But it was Cezar who decided
to sacrifice their own men.
You should sit down.
I'm sure you're tired.
Oh, would you like a change of clothes?
I can't get changed like this.
I'm sorry.
Only the Farsas royal family can undo that.
My grandfather borrowed it
from the Farsas treasury...
to use on you, once you came to this era.
Eh?
You seem alert now, so let me get to the point.
You see, I...
No, we are after Eleterria.
The red and blue magic spheres.
We want you to bring both of them to us.
How do you...
Know about them?
Or how do we plan to use them?
I'm plenty knowledgeable in these matters.
More than you are.
What do you plan to change
once you've obtained them?
I can't tell you yet.
If you choose to cooperate...
Tinasha!
Oscar!
Search the premises!
Yes!
I really can't let my eyes off you.
I'm sorry.
What is that?
It's a sealing ornament from your country.
I believe it works the same way as Akashia.
Is this the artifact stolen from
our treasury forty years ago?
How did you find me here?
I scoured all of Cezar with the barrier
you placed on me as a guide.
You did?
Even though the war just ended?
Well, my body was the key to detecting you.
Thank you very much.
Um, how's Sylvia doing?
Nothing severe.
She should be back on her feet
in a couple days or so.
Let us return.
Don't want to worry those waiting for us.
So they really are after the orbs...
But why would they need both of them?
Beats me.
Maybe there's a different way they can be used.
We'll look into it on our end, but you
should stay on guard for the time being.
They're targeting you.
Yes.
Also, you saved us from that evil god.
Thanks.
Your Majesty! Is now a good time?
Obviously not.
So? What do you want?
We received a visit from a woman
asking to meet Your Majesty.
Who?
Well...
I'm not sure.
Where are my guards?
Lavinia    Witch of Silence
I see my curse has been expertly broken.
Is the Witch Killer Queen responsible?
Your voice...
You're the Witch of Silence!
Long time no see.
You've grown.
Enough of your prattle.
Why are you here?
I was going to let you off with just the curse.
How incorrigible.
I'm left with no choice
now that it's been broken.
Lazar! Run for it!
Mila! Karr!
An interesting means of
protection you have there.
The work of your lovely bride?
It ends here!
Don't kill her, Oscar!
That's...
your grandmother.
Succumb to dreams from childhood.
What are you doing out here, Your Highness?
I just stepped out for a moment, Lazar.
And stop calling me Your Highness.
It feels weird.
Your Highness is Your Highness.
Ettard, it's time for today's training.
There's not much more I can teach you.
No need to be humble.
Please be my sparring partner.
As you wish.
Sometime next year, an energetic pupil
of mine should arrive at the palace.
His name is Als, and he's four years
older than Your Highness.
He's quite the skilled fighter.
Now that sounds exciting.
Oscar, draw Akashia.
Wait.
Draw Akashia from its scabbard, Oscar.
But...
It's okay. Have faith.
Tinasha...
Have you come to?
That can't be.
No one should be able to overwrite my spell.
I can't overwrite it, but I can exploit it.
I inserted my own dream.
My spell should only show childhood dreams.
That happens to be a childhood dream.
Don't think too much about it.
You would have been happier
if you'd stayed asleep.
It's meaningless if I'm the only one happy.
You are the child that must die...
to bring balance to the fate that was altered.
"The child that must die"?
Is that why you cast that curse on me?
Indeed.
The one you should condemn is your mother.
Oscar!
Thank goodness...
No.
I will not condemn my mother.
She defended me with her life.
So you remember?
Thanks to that dream earlier.
Mother...
Rosalia    Oscar's Mother
What's the matter, Oscar?
I see.
Mother went to the past to save my life.
You're my grandmother?
I do see a resemblance.
You sealed away my memories, didn't you?
You were the one who should have died.
The demonic spirit attacked you.
But Rosalia could not accept that reality.
She committed the sin of using
a magic sphere to distort the past.
Oscar!
Rosalia returned to before you were
attacked and managed to save your life.
However...
Rosalia ended up dying instead,
which complicated matters.
Even if the past is successfully altered,
it does not change the user's death.
Rosalia's lifespan was set the moment
she traded blows with the spirit,
and when that moment arrived...
She died without any warning.
As a result, Rosalia saved your life,
but killed your psyche.
You deserve neither blame nor hatred.
That said, you are someone
who should not be alive.
Which is why your blood
must not be passed down.
If you seek retribution for my mother's
deeds, I will readily take you on.
After all, I did the same thing.
The Witch Killer...
Is the reason you entered
the childhood dream...
I see now.
You fools!
Oscar!
I see it!
Why do you add to your sins?
Relive them?
Your actions may have had dire consequences.
The current me can't answer those questions.
But if she was suffering,
and I had the means...
I would save her no matter what.
Be it me who altered the past,
or some other force...
The present is what matters to me.
Even if it ends up warping this world?
Even so, I'll move forward from here.
Right now is all I have.
It may be absurd to say while pointing this
at you, but I don't want you to die.
I suppose it's asking for too much.
It really is.
Greed beyond selfishness.
She lifted the curse for you,
and now you seek to take her as well?
If that curse is what drew her to me,
perhaps I should be thanking you.
That woman is practically a witch.
If she bears your child,
that child will be a witch.
Is she so precious that you would
marry her with that knowledge?
She is.
Raising a witch as my child?
I do love a challenge.
How in the world did you raise him?
He's always been like this.
The day may come when you
wish you'd killed me here.
If it does, I'll kill you then.
Do as you like, then.
But do take care not to
commit any more follies,
lest the time come when you
need to balance everything out.
I'll keep that in mind.
How unwary of you,
after what happened yesterday.
It seemed like you had something to tell me.
I'm sure you know, but it'd be best
to seal away that orb.
I'll propose the idea.
On that note, why didn't you take the orb
out of Farsas after casting that curse?
I knew not where it was,
nor did I wish to search for it.
But seeing as how that idiot used it,
you know its whereabouts now?
It appears to be in the treasury.
But the orb he used is the one in Tuldarr.
Tuldarr?
There's more than one?
How much do you know about those orbs?
I could ask you the same thing.
I got it from a traveling fortune teller,
around two hundred years ago.
I was told that with the conviction,
you can go back in time to change
the past with that magic implement.
Conviction, you say...
What I know is that the magic
spheres are known as Eleterria,
and most likely there exist two of them.
The other one is under
seal in Tuldarr's treasury.
And there's a man who seeks to possess both.
That man is most likely
the one who told me about you two.
What? Valt did?
Take great caution.
Men like him won't hesitate
to do whatever it takes.
I'm grateful for your warning.
I'll be taking my leave.
Please wait!
Distorting the past and sacrificing
yourself to save someone...
Do you really think that's a sin?
No matter how much you love someone,
you mustn't change the way things should be,
to say nothing of
sacrificing yourself to do so.
The very height of foolishness.
You should know, as the one who was saved.
Excellent job breaking that curse.
The definition name just serves to protect
that idiot while sealing away his memories.
Pay it no mind.
Thank you very much.
How are you feeling?
A lot better now.
I forced you into a really demanding battle.
Sorry about that.
To be honest, I might have lost even
if I hadn't been watching out for you.
She was that strong?
We were up against a witch.
I only managed to break
her spell by sheer luck.
What's more, it felt like she was
holding back the entire time.
Is that right?
Tinasha, I'm sorry.
About what?
Four hundred years ago.
Eh?
Why are you the one apologizing?
I mean, I'm sure you must have your grievances.
Like why I decided to change the past,
or why I disappeared afterwards.
I wouldn't dare...
Until I was thirteen,
the world I knew was very small.
I was taken to the castle
right after I was born
and raised as the future queen candidate.
The only one I could call family
was the other candidate to be ruler.
The person I considered a brother
chose to sever ties with me.
It was then that he came into
my life and taught me so much.
I was happy every day I spent with him.
Not only did he save my life,
he showed me the love I needed
to walk onward by myself.
But when I came to this era
to try and repay him,
you turned out to be vicious and unkind to me,
unfriendly to foreign citizens,
blind to your own faults
but critical of others...
Hey, what's all this now?
But that unrelenting side
is what I like about you.
The you that's here now
is the one I want to stay with.
That's why...
I'm very happy now.
Thank you so much.
You're always there to save me.
Should you ever grow weak, or lose your magic,
I'll be there to compensate and protect you.
Whatever you may lose, I'll provide for you.
Oscar.
I'll be the one to protect you.
Listen here.
Try your best not to cause any problems.
This ceremony is a birthday
celebration for the king of Farsas!
I understand.
Do you really?
What's wrong, Travis?
I'll be right there.
By the way, the ribbon in your hair is loose.
Wh-What?
See? There we go.
Your beauty is unmatched, Aurelia.
Spare me the inane flattery.
Just don't do anything stupid.
~ Half of Eternity ~